engageiq.com 2013-06-07

# Welcome to Engage IQ

This privacy statement covers the site at [http://www.engageiq.com](http://www.engageiq.com/)

EngageIQ wants to demonstrate its commitment to its users' privacy so it invites public comment about this policy. The statement explains the following:   
1\. What personally identifiable information EngageIQ. collects.   
2\. That EngageIQ. does not share user information except in limited circumstances.   
3\. How EngageIQ. will notify users if it begins collecting more information.   
4\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in their information. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact 

Engage Logic, Inc.   
3080 Olcott Street Suite 130C   
Santa Clara, CA, 95054   
Or send email to [privacycomments@engageiq.com](mailto:privacycomments@engageiq.com)

**Information Collection**  
Engage Logic, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on the web site at http://www.Engageiq.com. Engage Logic, Inc. collects information from users at specific places on its web sites. 

Standard web sites use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. None of this information is linked to personally identifiable information. 

This web site automatically records the user's IP address to help diagnose problems with the server, and to administer the web site. IP address information is also used to track the popularity. The web server uses a cookie file to recognize users and remember certain preferences. The cookie is updated by the web server with each visit to the sit 

**Registration**

In order to become a publisher or advertiser, you must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic and other information.No contact information about membership to this web site will be publicly available. 

**Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law where we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us.

Business Transitions  
In the event Engage Logic, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Engage Logic, Inc. will notify users, via the procedure indicated below, prior to any change in this Privacy Statement as a result of a change in ownership or control of users' personal information. 

**Notification of Changes**   
Engage Logic, Inc. invites comment on its privacy policy and it reserves the right to make changes to this policy as necessary. Engage Logic, Inc. will post proposed changes to this privacy statement on a separate page at so that users are always aware of what information is collected and under what circumstances, if any, it gets disclosed. Engage Logic, Inc. will always use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at questions@engageiq.com. Or you may contact us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. As part of our business, we also provide links to third party sites. We encourage all of our advertisers to post their privacy policies on their sites and to adhere to the same high standard as is stated here. We, however, disclaim any responsibility for the actions of these third parties. AS A RESULT, WE ENCOURAGE OUR USERS TO READ THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THESE LINKED SITES, BECAUSE THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES MAY DIFFER FROM OURS. 

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:   
Engage Logic, Inc.   
3080 Olcott Street Suite 130C   
Santa Clara, CA, 95054
